xnumtw@gmail.com xnum@GitHub Taipei, Taiwan

Jia-Jun is a professional backend developer specializing in C++ and Go. He worked for Taipei Exchange at first that learned about classical financial system. Afterward he joined blockchain startup as a senior developer, and becomes team lead who is responsible for cryptocurrency exchange. Now to construct competitive product, he is bringing bleeding-edge technology to Fin Tech startup.

Work Experience

July 2019-Present Sky Mirror Technology Co., Ltd. VP of Engineering

In charge of futures trading system DevOps.

June 2018-May 2019 COBINHOOD, Ltd. Lead Backend developer

Cryptocurrency exchange development.

Led 5 people exchange team.

- Optimized Kubernetes deployment configuration to reduce monthly cost over 10000 USD on Google Cloud Platform.
- Designed new coin holder rewards point system to reduce 99% computing resource.
 Developed staking rewards distributing service for hundreds of users.
- Implemented Go version client library to integrate 2 blockchains (Monero, Tezos) into exchange.
- Improved testing with database/cache tuning to speed up 300%.

June 2017-June 2018 Taipei Exchange Software Engineer

Emerging stock trading system development.

- Proposed state-of-the-art stock trading system design based on raft consensus to remove commercial middleware dependency.
- Developed message dispatch proxy to adapt trading system to web service.

 Optimized continuous data streaming system to 110 times faster and solved critical race condition problems, also developed a cross-platform new one by event-driven design.

Education

2015-2017 2011-2015 MSc, Institute of Computer Science and Engineering National Chiao Tung University BSc, Computer Science National Taichung University of Education

Skills

- C++, Go, git, docker, Kubernetes
- PostgreSQL, MySQL, redis, NATS streaming, gRPC